https://www.studiothink.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Our Commitment
It is our commitment to maintain the principles of integrity and trust
with respect to the protection of personal information. As part of our
commitment, we will protect the privacy of personal information of
employees, clients, customers and other individuals whose personal
information we collect, use and disclose. We are committed to complying
with British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act (the “Act”)
and all other applicable privacy laws.
Definitions
“business contact information” means information that enables an
individual to be contacted at work, including his/her name, title,
business address, business telephone number, fax number and e-mail
address.
“employee personal information” means personal information about an
employee that is collected used or disclosed solely for the purposes
reasonably required to establish, manage or terminate an employment
relationship, but does not include other personal information about the
employee.
“personal information” means any information that personally identifies
an individual, but does not include business contact information or work
product information.
”work product information” means information prepared or collected by an
individual or group of individuals as part of their employment or
business responsibilities or activities related to their employment or
business.
Responsibility
We are responsible for all personal information under our control, even
if it is not in our possession. We have developed policies and
procedures to deal with the proper collection, use and disclosure of
personal information.
Purposes
We collect personal information for the following purposes:
>  to individualize your experience on our website
>  to communicate separately with you
>  to facilitate your movements throughout our website
>  to be able to selectively send you communications that may be of interest to you, either electronically or otherwise
>  other
Consent
We require the consent of individuals to collect, use or disclose
personal information. Unless required by law or otherwise authorized by
the Act, we will not use or disclose personal information already
collected for other purposes unless we obtain the consent of the
individual to whom it belongs. Generally, we will seek consent to use
and disclose personal information at the same time as we collect the
information. We will affirmatively ask to join our mailing lists using
the forms provided on this website or other means expressly sanctioned
by us. Subject to contractual or legal arrangements, you may withdraw or
refuse consent provided that we are given reasonable notice. We will
inform you of the consequences of withdrawing your consent, if any.
Unsubscribe Policy
We strive to only send e-mails to those who want to receive it. If you
would not like to receive future e-mails from us, reply to any email
with UNSUBSCRIBE as the subject.
Collection
We will only collect personal information for the purposes we have
identified above and that are reasonable in the circumstances. We will
only collect personal information through methods that are lawful, will
not collect information indiscriminately and will try to collect
personal information directly from the individual concerned unless
authorized by that individual to collect it from a third party or
otherwise as permitted by the Act. Depending on how you have configured
your browser, when you access our website, a small file – a “cookie” –
may be created by our server and stored on your computer. The cookie
contains a unique session identification number and is used to:
>  keep track of your online order
>  ensure that you see the correct products and pricing applicable to the province in which you are located
>  personalize your experience by alerting you to features and information that might interest you
other
A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise the data on
your hard drive. If you arrive at our website with your browser
configured to disable cookies, you will not be identified until you
register and sign-in. Please be advised that cookies may be required to
complete certain functions on this website, such as making purchases or
placing orders at our online store.
Aggregate Information
We collect certain aggregate information, such as tracking the Internet
address of the domains from which you visit our site and analyzing this
data for trends and statistics, tracking your IP address (the number
that is automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the
Web), and tracking your browser type. We use this aggregate information
to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our website,
and to gather broad demographic information. None of this information is
connected with your personal information. We may also generate
non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information
provided during registration (such as the total number, but not the
names, of clients).
Use of IP Addresses
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your
computer whenever you’re surfing the Internet. Web servers automatically
identify your computer by its IP address. We may collect IP addresses
for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregated
information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our website.
When clients request pages from our website, our servers log the
requesting clients’ IP addresses. We normally will not link IP addresses
to anything personally identifiable, which means that clients’ sessions
will be logged, but client identity remains anonymous to us. We can and
will use IP addresses to identify a client when we feel it is necessary
to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect
our service, website, or any person, or where it is otherwise authorized
or required by law.
Use, Disclosure and Retention
We will only use or disclose personal information for the purpose(s) for
which it was collected. We may disclose the personal information to:
>  a person who in our reasonable judgment is seeking the information as an agent of the individual
>  a company or individual engaged by us to perform functions on its behalf, such as research or data processing
>  a credit reporting agency
>  a public authority or agent of a public authority, if in our
reasonable judgment, it appears that there is imminent danger to life or
property which could be avoided or minimized by disclosure of the
information
>  where you consent to such disclosure or it is required or authorized by law
We may use and disclose employee personal information for a variety
of purposes related to commencing, managing or terminating the
employment relationship. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any
personal information collected at our site, including contact forms,
download requests or email lists. We will retain personal information
only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes stated above, as
required for legal or business purposes or as required by law.
Subsequently, we will destroy, erase, or make anonymous such
information. However, we will retain for at least one-year personal
information that has been used to make a decision about a client,
customer or employee.
Accuracy of Personal Information
We will make reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information in
our control is accurate and complete. You may request corrections to
your personal information. If your request for a correction is rejected
by us, we will make a notation of such request and rejection on your
file or personal information.
Safeguarding Personal Information
We will protect personal information in your control against risks of
loss, theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification
or destruction by security safeguards that are appropriate to the
sensitivity and format of the information.
Access
Upon reasonable written notice from you, we will, within 30 days or such
longer period in the event we obtain an extension, provide access to
all your personal information in our possession and tell your what the
information is being used for and to whom it has been disclosed. We
reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for providing access to
personal information. If we refuse your request for access, we will
notify you in writing, documenting the reasons for refusal, the relevant
provision of the Act on which we rely and resources for redress
available to you, including from the British Columbia Information and
Privacy Commissioner.
Complaints
If you have complaints about how your personal information is being
handled by us, you may file a written complaint. Such complaint must
clearly state the nature of the dispute and contain all necessary
contact information for you. We will acknowledge receipt of a complaint,
investigate such complaint and notify you of the outcome of the
complaint, including any relevant steps taken. If a complaint has not
been resolved to your satisfaction, you may seek redress with the
British Columbia Information and Privacy Commissioner.
Links to Other Sites
We are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of
websites to which our website may link and our privacy policy does not
apply to those websites. These other websites may send their own cookies
to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Please keep in
mind that whenever you give out personal information online (for
example, via message boards or chat lines), that information can be
collected and used by people you don’t know. While we strive to protect
our clients’ personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of
any information you disclose online, you disclose such information at
your own risk.
Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our
policy to comply with applicable laws. We recommend that children ask a
parent for permission before sending personal information to us or to
anyone else online.
Revisions to this Policy
To ensure that this Policy is up to date and complies with the Act, we
reserve the right to make changes, which will become effective 30 days
following our providing notice thereof.
Work with us.
Get free wine.
Get free wine.
Just kidding. But we will send you our latest articles and inspiration once a month, plus, you can unsubscribe at any time. Don't leave without becoming a Studiothink insider.
If you are human, leave this field blank.
